Guide to the Garden Club of Allegheny County Records, 1913-2012 AIS.2006.07
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Reports, 1914-2008; II.
  - Committee Reports, 1942-2008; 4.
    - Long Range Planning Committee - Pennsylvania Association for Sustainable Agriculture (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Long Range Planning Committee - Powdermill Nature Reserve (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Long Range Planning Committee - Riverlife Taskforce (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Meetings Committee, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Optional Day Committee, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Outdoor Garden Committee, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Phipps and Hunt, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Plant Exchange Committee, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Printing Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Program Committee, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Public Relations Bulletin (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Public Relations (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Public Relations, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Standing Committee, 1942 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Steering Committee (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Summary of Committees, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - President's Papers and Reports, 1916-2000; 5.
    President's minutes are overviews of activities and general meetings as collected by the president of the GCAC. The minutes are mainly typed, but the earliest are hand written. Also included are the personal papers and notebooks of two former Presidents.
    - President's Reports, 1916-1926 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - President's Reports, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - President's Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - President's Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - President's Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Audrey Hilliard President's Notebook, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Parie Dugan Papers, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Annual Questionnaire for Club Presidents, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Photo of Low, Dudley, Gilmore and Abel (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Events, 1914-2009; III.
  This series contains material related to projects and events held by the GCAC. Several files in this series contain visual material, including photographs from the 1961 Old Economy Kitchen Garden Restoration Project and a VHS tape documenting the GCA trip to Japan that same year. Included in this series are announcements for and invitations to GCAC flowers shows, annual meeting programs, awards and certificates and information about a wide variety of garden, conservation and horticultural projects. This series is divided into five subseries: Flower and Garden Shows, Awards and Certificates, Activities and Events, Conservation and Horticulture. The material in this subseries dates from 1914 to 2009.
  - Flower and Garden Shows, 1935-2006; 1.
    This subseries consists of announcements, invitations and programs for flower and garden shows that were sponsored by the GCAC or the Sewickley Horticultural Society, which is affiliated with the GCAC. The main attractions at flower show are the exhibits, which range in size from garden displays with elaborate landscaping to individual and club entries of prize horticultural specimens. At each show, an official theme provides the inspiration for exhibits. The exhibits are submitted for judging by category, some of which are highly competitive. Included in the subseries are several judging guidebooks that judges at GCAC events used. The GCAC also held smaller flower shows such as the annual Chrysanthemum Exhibitions and Spring Flower Shows in Pittsburgh. Announcements of these annual competitions are included in this subseries.
    - Exhibition Committee Report (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Fall Horticultural Show, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Flower Show and Judging Guide Book, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Flower Show and Judging Guide Books, 1974 & 1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Flower Shows - Photos and Programs, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - GCAC Flower Show, 1947-1964 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - GCAC Flower Show, 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - GCAC Flower Show, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - GCAC Flower Show, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - GCAC Flower Show and Lecture Invitation (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - GCAC Invitation (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Horticultural Judges Rules and Agendas, 1976-1989 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Invitations and Programs for Various Flower Shows (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Procedure for Organizing a GCA Flower Show, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Rules and Entry Forms for Various Flower Shows (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Tips for Flower Show Schedules (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Zone V Flower Show, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Zone V Flower Shows, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Zone V Flower Show, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Zone V Flower Show, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Flower Shows - How to Exhibit Lecture (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - GCAC Chrysanthemum Exhibition Announcement, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - GCAC Spring Flower Show Announcement, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Sewickley Horticultural Society Chrysanthemum Show Program, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - GCAC Exhibition Announcement, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Sewickley Flower Show Final Program, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - GCAC Spring Flower Show Announcement, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Sewickley Horticultural Society Chrysanthemum Show Announcement, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - GCAC Exhibition Announcement, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - GCAC Exhibition Announcement, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Sewickley Horticultural Society Chrysanthemum Show Announcement, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - GCAC Contest Invitation, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - GCAC Exhibitions Committee Show Invitation, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - GCAC Spring Flower Show Announcement, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Sewickley Horticultural Society Chrysanthemum Show Announcement, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - GCAC Spring Flower Show Announcement, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Sewickley Horticultural Society Chrysanthemum Show Announcement, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - GCAC Annual Competition for the New York Flower Show Announcement, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - GCAC Rose Show Announcement, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - GCAC Annual Competition for the New York Flower Show Announcement, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Sewickley Horticultural Society Chrysanthemum Show Announcement, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - GCAC June Flower Show Announcement, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - GCAC June Flower Show Announcement, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Fall Flower Show Announcement, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - The Flowers of America by Jeanne Holgate Exhibition Lecture, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - GCAC June Flower Show Invitation, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Bryant Park Flower Show Invitation and Schedule, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Zone V Flower Show Entry Form, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Flower Show Workshop Entry Form, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Flower Arranging Workshop Brochure, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Flower Shows Are Fun! Booklet, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Awards and Certificates, 1936-2008; 2.
    This subseries contains documents that relate to awards issued to both individual members as well as the entire GCAC. Some files document the nominations, selective process, and criteria determined by the GCAC for awards given by the GCA. Other materials simply describe the nature and the nominating process for awards and flower shows.
    - Allegheny County Bicentennial Flower and Garden Contest, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Amy Angell Collier Medal Certificate, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Annual Awards Dinner, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Annual Dinner Medal Award Program, 1985 & 1986 & 1988 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Application for State Award, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Awards and Records Committee Report, 1954-1955 & 1957 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Awards Committee Final Report, June 2008 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Awards Committee Objective Report, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Awards Committee Report, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Awards Committee Reports and Documents, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Awards Committee Reports and Documents, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Certificate of Appreciation, Karen Meck, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Club Awards, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Conservation Achievement Certificate, Audrey Hilliard, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Distinguished Daughters of Pennsylvania Award, 1955-1956 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Distinguished Daughters of Pennsylvania Award, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Dorothy Falcon Platt Award, 1972-1988 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Dorothy Falcon Platt Award Nomination and Certificate, Mary Berger, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Frances K. Hutchinson Medal, Jack Heinz Nomination, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Garden Federation of Pennsylvania, Laurels Certificate for Civic Development, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - GCA Achievement Medal Nomination, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - GCA Achievement Medal Nomination, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - GCA Activities and Medal Awards, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - GCA Awards List, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - GCA Flower Arrangement Certificate, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - GCA Founder's Fund Award Winners, 1936-1979 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - GCA Funds and Awards Recipients, 1936-1986 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - GCA National Medals Guide, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - GCA National Medals Guide, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - GCA National Medals Pamphlet, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - GCA Autumn in the Atrium, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Historic Preservation Achievement Award, 1982 & 1999 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Hunt Trophy, 1943-1960 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Hunt Trophy, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Hunt Trophy Award Form and Certificate, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Living Treasure Award, Sherley T. Blaxter, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Massachusetts Horticultural Society Medal, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Medal Awards Committee, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Medal of Honor Nomination, David Leach, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Medal of Honor Nomination, Ralph E. Griswold, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Medal of Merit, Mary Brown, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Medal of Merit, Edith Fisher, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Medal of Merit in Horticulture, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Medal of Merit in Horticulture, Mary Weidlein, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Medalists, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Montague Award, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Oakley Thorn Medal Certificate, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Pittsburgh History and Landmark Foundation Award of Merit, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Preservation Award Certificate, May 1999 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Sears and Roebuck Award Application, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Take Pride in Pennsylvania Award, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Zone V Conservation and Civic Improvement Award Nomination, Christina Schmidlapp, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Zone V Conservation Award Nomination, Elizabeth D. Littell Childs, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Zone V Creative Leadership Award Nomination, Paula Sculley, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Zone V Horticulture Award Nomination, Elizabeth D. Littell Childs, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Zone V Leadership Medal Nomination, Susan Clancy, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Activities and Events, 1914-2009; 3.
    This subseries documents some of the activities and events that were sponsored, attended, or developed by GCAC. These include civic activities, garden planting plans, conservation activities and educational materials. Also contained in this subseries is the Master Plan for Mellon Park, Phipps Outdoor Garden Project, Pizzazz, and Northside Project. This series also documents the GCAC's restoration of the Old Economy kitchen garden and the 1961 GCA's trip to Japan. Several members of the GCAC took part in this trip, and the items in this subseries document the gardens the club visited and events they attended while in Japan.
    - Allee of Trees, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Allegheny Commons, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Allegheny Commons, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Allegheny Commons: History (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Allegheny Commons Tree Conservation (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Anne Chalfant Mitchell Memorial Garden, 1936-1963 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Amazon Center for Environmental Education and Research Foundation (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Ambler School of Horticulture, 1949-1957 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Art in Bloom, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Associated Artists of Pittsburgh, 1948-1957 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Audubon Center for Native Plants (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Autumn in the Atrium, 1981-1988 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Betsy Fuller Inc. Fundraiser (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Billboard Ban on Scenic Byways, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Bluebirds, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Botany in Action, 1995-2000 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Botany in Action, 1996-1998 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Botany in Action, 2000-2003 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Botany in Action, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Botany in Action, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Botany in Action, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Botany in Action Grants, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Botany in Action: History (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Botany in Action Mentors (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Botany in Action: Phipps News (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Botanical Bingo (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Brown Chapel, Letter from Lady Bird Johnson, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Brown Chapel Neighborhood Project, 1970-1985 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Brown Chapel Neighborhood Project, 1985-2004 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Brown Chapel Photos of Window Box Project (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Camp Reynold, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Carnegie Museum Carriage Entrance, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Carnegie Museum Carriage Entrance, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Celebration of the Tomato Visit to Heinz Plant, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Civic Planting and Projects Committee, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Chronological List of Events, 1914-1954 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Consumer Guide to Farm Products and Local Food, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Cultural Pageant Program, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Dixmont State Hospital Civil Project Proposal (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Donations to School, 1919-1945 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Donations and Memorials (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Earth Partners (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Ecoforum, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Fern Hollow Nature Center (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Floral Impressionism: Watercolors by Sharon Klay Exhibition Invite, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Fort Ligonier Memorial Foundation Trip, 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Founders Fund, 1957-1961 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Founders Fund, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Founders Fund, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Founders Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Founders Fund, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Frick Environmental Center (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Garden Club Federation of Pennsylvania, 1945-1961 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Garden Club Federation of Pennsylvania, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Garden Club Federation of Pennsylvania, 1996-1998 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Garden Club Federation of Pennsylvania, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Garden Club Federation of Pennsylvania, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Garden Club Federation of Pennsylvania Award Manual (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Garden Club Federation of Pennsylvania, Club President's Handbook, August 1996 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Garden Conservancy, Open Days Directory, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Garden History and Design Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Garden History and Design Committee, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Garden History and Design Committee, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Garden History and Design Committee: Smithsonian Institute, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Garden Descriptions, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Garden Maintenance, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Gardens Campaign, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Green Elephant Show Flyer, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Griswold Design for Carnegie Institute, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Grow Pittsburgh - Sponsors (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Historic Garden Week, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Hunt Botanical Library, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Japan Trip - Itinerary, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Japan Trip - Program Booklet, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Japan Trip - GCA 48th Annual Meeting Program Booklet, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Japan Trip - Dinner Invitations, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Japan Trip - Facts About Japan Newsletter, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Japan Trip - Gagaku (Imperial Music and Dance) Program, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Japan Trip - Tourist Brochures, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Japan Trip - Video (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Japan Trip - Welcome Dinner Program, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Japan and Hawaii Postcards, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Jennie King Mellon Garden Finances, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Joyce Chen - Scissors (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Junior Project Program, 1948-1952 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Katherine Grosscup Scholarship, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Keystone Commons Buildings (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - L. Smith Bird Sales, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - L. Smith Bird Sales, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Leonard and Leonard Landscaping at Allegheny Hospital, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Manchester Project of Pittsburgh, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - May Market, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - May Market, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - May Market, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - May Market, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - May Market, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - May Market, 2004-2006 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - May Market, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - May Market - Press (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - McAdoo Rugs Records, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - McAdoo Rugs Records, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - McAdoo Rugs Records, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - McAdoo Rugs Price Lists and Samples, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - McAdoo Rugs Samples and Photographs (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - McAdoo Rugs Preview Contributions (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - McAdoo Rugs Raffle (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Medicinal Gardens, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Medicinal Plant Project, 1998-2001 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Medicinal Plant Project Report, 2000-2003 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Medicinal Plant Project Report and Programs and Press, 1998-2003 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Mellon Park, 1951-2000 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Mellon Park Garden Place News, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Mellon Park Master Plan, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Mellon Park Preservation and Management Plan, 8/30/1999 & 11/08/1999 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Mellon Park Preservation and Management Plan, May 2000 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Messerve Book Sales, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Garden Clubs (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Neighborhood Gardens (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Neighborhood Gardens Project Photos, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Neighborhood Gardens Project Script (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Neighborhood Gardens Project Slides (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services Parklet, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Neville House - Master Plan Book, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Neville House - National Trust Pamphlet (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Neville House - Proposal and Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Neville House - Urban Design Book, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Northside Garden Block Program (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Northside Photos and Negatives, 1973-1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Northside Project Scrapbook, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Northside Projects, 1971-1975 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Old Economy Kitchen Garden, 1929-1963 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Old Economy Kitchen Garden Restoration Project, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Old Economy Kitchen Garden Restoration Project Blueprints, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Old Post Office - Northshore, 1966-1981 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Park Place Drawings (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Partners for Plants Project, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania Association for Sustainable Agriculture (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Phipps Conservatory, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Phipps Conservatory Friends, 1987-1989 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Phipps Conservatory Press and Programs, 1990 & 2001 & 2008 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Phipps Conservatory Sculptures, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens - History (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Luncheon, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Memorial Contributions (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration Budget, 1986-1989 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration Construction, 1986-1988 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration Drawings (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration Design Contracts, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration Design Contracts, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration Fencing, 1986-1988 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Restoration Project Plan, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Phipps Outdoor Gardens Training Guides, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Civic Garden Center (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Civic Garden Center - May Market, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Civic Garden Center Newsletter (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Garden Center and Market (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Parks Conservancy, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Parks Conservancy, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Parks Conservancy, 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Parks Conservancy Press (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh Regional Planning Association, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Pizzazz, 1996-1998 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Pizzazz Ad Hoc Committee Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Pizzazz Botany in Action, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Pizzazz Botany in Action Financial Records, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Pizzazz CD-Rom, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Pizzazz Donations, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Pizzazz Donations, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Pizzazz Donations, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Pizzazz Donations and Deposits, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Pizzazz Donations and Deposits, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Pizzazz Fanfare Magazine, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Pizzazz Financial Reports, 1994-1996 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Pizzazz Financial Reports, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Pizzazz Financial Reports, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Pizzazz Financial Reports, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Pizzazz Financial Reports, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Pizzazz Financial Statements, 1998-2001 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Pizzazz General Financial Information (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Pizzazz General Financial Information, 1994-1996 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Pizzazz Invitations, 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 11)